foodics.com 2019-12-03

# Privacy Policy | Foodics

This Privacy Policy is intended to inform you that **Alwans **Strategy for  **International Technology** and our affiliates ( **we** or **the Company** ) may collect information from users of the Foodics cloud-based iPad point-of-sale (POS) restaurant management and operational system.

This includes all hardware, products and services offered by the Company including our websites, products, services and software applications we own or control, and all associated services and add-ons including third party services (the Services).

This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, share and protect such information. By registering on our websites and using our Services in any way, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy. We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time. Your continued use of our Services after changes are posted constitutes your agreement to the changes. Your privacy is important to us. If you do not agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy, please discontinue your use of the Services:

  1. We certainly do not collect information about you unless we need them.
  2. We do not share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, improve our Services, or protect our rights.
  3. We do not store your personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our Services.

### Information we collect

We collect the following types of information:

**Information you give us directly.**

We collect information you provide when you access or participate in certain aspects of our Services, such as when you create any type of account, use our Services, make purchases, leave a review, complete a survey or benefit from any of our promotions.

The information you provide may specifically identify you, and include: your name, email address, postal mailing address, business address, telephone numbers, payment information (including payment card numbers), use of Services.

The amount and type of information you provide depends on the nature of the interaction. You may always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent you from using our corresponding Services.

In addition to the information mentioned above, you may provide information about you, but that does not identify you, such as your age, gender, zip code, interests, preferences with respect to our Services.

**Information automatically collected when you use or access our Services**

_**Cookies.**_ Like most online services, we may use Cookies and other technologies, such as web beacons, web storage, and unique advertising identifiers, to collect information about your activity, browser, and device.

A browser cookie is a small piece of data that is stored on your device to help websites remember things about you. Other technologies, including web storage and identifiers associated with your device, may be used for similar purposes. In this Privacy Policy, we say Cookies (the Cookies) to discuss all of these technologies.

We may also use these Cookies to collect information when you interact with our Services offered through one of our partners, such as advertising and commerce features. Most web browsers are set to accept Cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually remove or reject browser Cookies through the settings on your browser or device.

Keep in mind, though, that removing or rejecting Cookies could affect the availability and functionality of our Services. The Company may use Cookies for a number of reasons, like protecting your data and account, helping us see which features are most popular, counting visitors to a page, improving our users’ experience, keeping our Services secure, and just generally providing you with a better, more intuitive, and satisfying experience.

The Cookies we use generally fall into one of the following categories: (i) preferences: we use these Cookies to remember your settings and preferences. (e.g.: languages…); (ii) security: we use these Cookies to help identify and prevent security risks; (iii) performance: we use these cookies to collect information about how you interact with our Services and to help us improve them. (e.g.: to determine if you have interacted with a certain page).

_**Device identifiers.**_ When you use our Services, including but not limited to, when you install software, download any type of Services or access the Services, on your computer, tablet, mobile device or any other devices, we collect device-specific identifiers and mobile network information including phone number, device type, device identifier and operating system.

We may also collect information about your location and request access to certain rights on your devices, such as access to storage. A device identifier may be data stored in connection with the device hardware, data stored in connection with the device's operating system or other software, or data sent to the device by the Company. Some features of the Service may not function properly if use or availability of device identifiers is impaired or disabled.

### How we use the information

In addition to some of the specific uses of information this Privacy Policy covers, we may use information that we receive in order to: (i) develop, operate, improve, deliver, maintain, and protect our Services; (ii) send you communications, including by email. For example, we may use email to respond to support inquiries or to share information about our Services, and promotional offers that we think may interest you; (iii) monitor and analyze trends and usage; (vii) enhance the safety and security of our Services; (viii) verify your identity and prevent fraud or other unauthorized or illegal activity; (ix) use information we’ve collected from Cookies and other technology to enhance the Services and your experience with them; (x) enforce our Terms and Conditions and other usage policies.

### Sharing of your information

The Company discloses your information to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need that information in connection with the Services and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using the Services, you consent to the transfer of such information to them to the extent permissible under applicable law.

We may share your information with our corporate entities including any holding company, affiliates and subsidiaries. If the Company gets involved in a merger, asset sale, financing, liquidation or bankruptcy, or acquisition of all or some portion of our business to another company, we may share your information with that company before and after the transaction closes.

We may also share your information with service providers, resellers, and partners to provide or support our or their services, payment processing, financing services or credit review or that help the Company market to customers or improve the user experience for our customers and their end users.

For example, we may share your information with companies which provide services such as information processing, extending credit, fulfilling customer orders, delivering products to you, managing and enhancing customer data, providing customer service, and conducting customer research or satisfaction surveys.

These companies are obligated to protect your information and may be located wherever the Company operates. If you are approved for service, your account will be governed by the Company’s and its distributor or carrier’s respective privacy policies. Personal information will only be shared by us to provide or improve our products, services and advertising and corporate communications; it will not be shared with third parties for their marketing purposes.

We may share your information with other third parties for legal reasons. We may share information about you if we reasonably believe that disclosing the information is needed to: (a) comply with any valid legal process, governmental request, or applicable law, rule, or regulation; (b) investigate, remedy, or enforce potential Terms and Conditions violations; (c) protect the rights, property, and safety of us, our users, or others; (d) detect and resolve any fraud or security concerns. We may access, preserve and share your information in response to a legal request if we have a good faith belief that the law requires us to do so.

This may include responding to legal requests from jurisdictions outside of the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia where we have a good faith belief that the response is required by law in that jurisdiction, affects users in that jurisdiction, and is consistent with internationally recognized standards.

We may also access, preserve and share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to protect ourselves, you and others, including as part of investigations; and to prevent death or imminent bodily harm. Information we receive about you may be accessed, processed and retained for an extended period of time when it is the subject of a legal request or obligation, governmental investigation, or investigations concerning possible violations of our terms or policies, or otherwise to prevent harm.

### Third party sites and services

You may be given the opportunity to register with us or use our Services via third party accounts. These services will authenticate your identity and may provide you the option to share certain information (such as your name and email address) with us. We may store the information you provide us through such accounts and combine it with other information, including Personally Identifying Information.

The Services may contain links to third-party websites, products, and services. Our Services may also use or offer Services from third parties − for example, a third-party service provider, distributor, or application. Information collected by third parties, which may include such things as location data or contact details, is governed by their privacy practices. We encourage you to learn about the privacy practices of those third parties.

### Revisions to our Privacy Policy

We may modify or update this Privacy Policy from time to time. But when we do, we’ll let you know one way or another. Sometimes, we’ll let you know by revising the date at the top of the Privacy Policy that’s available on our website. If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy or data processing, please contact us at **[international@foodics.com](mailto:international@foodics.com).**
